So I've got three things to say.
So stay for the whole thing.
First, the 22nd of January began the new TikTok algorithm.
And that is simply just writing on the wall of all of these apps that are run by Zio's.
Patreon is one of the few spaces on this interwebs that is not Zio owned.
Thus, I'll be interacting with this app a bit differently.
So what I'd like to suggest is that one, you make sure to subscribe to my newsletter.
And two, that you go over to Patreon.
And if you cannot afford the $5 subscription fee, at least do the free subscription.
You will still continue to get content and you will get more if you do the $5 subscription.
And thus, that's where you'll see my in-person commentary as well as on my show,
Views for Amanda Land on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV, every Wednesday, 10 a.m. Eastern.
Second, any black people you see talking about I Rock With MAGA are the same folks who talk about,
Yeah, I'll hustle in my hood because at the end of the day, somebody gonna do it.
So why shouldn't it be me?
It's not about any political ideology.
It's about straight selfishness, period.
Folks can be street smart while also being spiritually dumb.
Third, let's look at some books that I purchased.
Shout out to the homie Chill Moody out there in Philly.
He wrote this book, Gia the Golfer.
Go and support him.
Also got me another children's book from Jenen Matari, Everything Grows in Jido's Garden.
This talks about Palestine and the connection to the earth.
Speaking of connections to earth, I got Farming While Black,
Soul Fire Farms Practical Guide to Liberation on the Land.
And remember, if we are connected to the earth, we are now gaining not just sustenance in the food,
but also power from the earth.
Speaking of which, women who run with wolves, myths and stories of the wild woman archetype.
I look forward to reading it because I do feel like I have a dire wolf.
The Empath Survival Guide, Life Strategies for Sensitive People.
If you are like me and you are hypersensitive and you are in a world that is completely chaotic,
which is a lot of us, this might be able to help us.
So I'm going to be checking this out.
And speaking of a chaotic world, our American Israel, the story of an entangled alliance.
This right here speaks to the next phase of the chaos that we are in.
Have a good weekend.
If you're working for somebody that you don't respect, may you be nonproductive.
Shout out to Minneapolis.
Empower to all the people who consider integrity an integral part of their resistance.
Support a real one.